(INSECTS CHIRRING)
(CROWS CAWING IN DISTANCE)
(HORSE NEIGHING)
BOY: No!
(HORSE WHEEZING)
(HORSE WHIMPERS SOFTLY)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
- (HORSE CRIES OUT)
- Oh!
(PANTING)
(SIGHS)
(HORSE GROANS)
MAN: When someone
you love dies...
(HORSE NEIGHING)
...you will know emptiness.
- (WIRE SNAPS FROM TENSION)
- (BOY SCREAMS)
(CROWS CAWING)
You will know what it is
to be completely
and utterly alone.
You will never forget...
(CROWS CAWING)
...and you will never...
ever forgive.
(ROGUISH ELECTRONIC
MUSIC PLAYING)
(TRAINS RUMBLING)
(PHONE VIBRATING)
(SIGHS)
- Zadie?
- Shelly.
Did you see what I sent you?
SHELLY: No. What is it?
I showed the video to someone.
I think they found out.
What the fuck is going on?
Check your texts.
(LAUGHTER ON VIDEO)
MAN: Hey, Shelly.
WOMAN: Oh, stop!
(GASPS SOFTLY)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
ZADIE: What the fuck?
What did you do to her?
Where did you get this?
Dom shot it.
Look, we can get him with this.
He's not invincible, Shelly.
Yes, he is.
I'm getting my shit
and getting the fuck out.
Come with me.
You and Dom.
The three of us.
Why the fuck did you do this?
ZADIE: It's not safe
for us here anymore.
SHELLY: Stay there.
I'm coming to you.
ZADIE: I think
they've got someone on me.
If they're following me,
they're following you.
WOMAN 2: Hello, Zadie.
SHELLY: Zadie?
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Zadie?
(LAUGHTER ON VIDEO)
MAN: Hey, Shelly.
WOMAN: Oh, stop!
WOMAN 2: There were
other options, Zadie.
I wish you'd talked to me first.
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERING)
(ZADIE CHOKES)
(GASPS)
(LINE RINGING)
Hi, you've reached Dom.
Leave a message.
Dom, it's me.
Zadie's lost her fucking mind.
She just sent me
some video that you shot.
Meet me at Zadie's.
I'm gonna check on her.
(CUPBOARD SCRAPES)
(GRUNTS)
(BUTTON CLICKING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(TRAIN RUMBLES)
(FAINT ANNOUNCEMENT ON PA)
OFFICER: Whoa, whoa.
What're you doing, huh?
- (GRUNTS)
- Yeah, we have a 10-50, female in her 20s.
Bringing her in.
- (ENGINE STARTS)
- (SIREN WHOOPS)
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
INMATE 1: Say something.
INMATE 2: Wake up, Eric.
Are you gonna
stand up for yourself?
INMATE 1: Look at me.
INMATE 2:
What're you gonna do about it?
You're fucking old enough
to look after yourself.
INMATE 2:
Daddy's gonna come back.
- INMATE 1: We're here.
- Say something.
- Hello. Are you there?
- Say something!
- Nothin'? You got nothin'?
- Where's your mom right now?
(HORSE CRIES OUT)
Say something, son!
- Wake the fuck up.
- Say something, man!
(ECHOING SCREAM)
Say fucking something!
THERAPIST: I know
this is hard, Eric.
But these exercises
are meant to get you past
the destructive behaviors
that brought you here.
Burying it... using drugs...
(SCOFFS)
That's the easy way out.
It's what allows you
to hide that pain away.
You, uh, going to join us?
You know, Hemingway wrote,
"The world breaks everyone,
"and afterwards,
"many are strong
at the broken places.
"But those
that will not break...
"it kills."
(CLINKS)
(CELL DOOR BUZZES, OPENS)
(DOOR SHUTS)
...group therapy after that.
No phones.
No talking after dark.
No fraternizing with the men.
(GRIM MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC SOARS, FADES)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
MAN: Mr. Roeg.
Here's the young protege
from Vienna
I was telling Marion about.
It's a pleasure to meet you,
Mr. Roeg.
Please.
Sit.
Now, you know
I was born in Vienna,
a cradle of immortal music.
I've lived long enough to see
some of the greats play.
They tell me that
you're quite dynamic yourself.
- May I borrow you?
- Yes.
Um...
I look forward
to hearing you play.
What is it?
We found her.
(STOOL SCRAPING)
(CLANGS)
(ZADIE GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(GASPS SOFTLY)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
MR. ROEG: It's all right, Zadie.
It's all right.
What's done is done.
We're looking for your friends.
Have you seen Shelly?
No.
You're a good person, Zadie.
You wouldn't tell me
if you knew.
Would you?
I've killed hundreds
of innocents like you
in the centuries
that I've been here.
It never gets any easier.
(MR. ROEG EXHALES)
I wish
the murderers and rapists,
and scum of the earth would do,
but...
they go to hell already,
you see.
Whereas people like you,
those are the souls
that he wants.
That's the... the deal I made.
You go to hell
so I don't have to.
(TEARFULLY) Please...
Please let me go.
You can go.
(DEMONIC WHISPERING)
(CLANKS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BLADE SCRAPES)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROANING)
(CHOKING)
(GRUNTS)
(CHILLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(MAN SHOUTING INSTRUCTIONS)
What the fuck is going on here?
Get your shit together!
You know why we still out here?
It's because of your bullshit!
Huh?
(ALL PANTING)
Hi.
They don't like you in here,
do they?
No, not really.
They have a thing about
men and women
not sitting together.
SHELLY: I know.
They told me.
I like your tattoo.
Thanks.
ERIC: "Laugh now. Cry later."
It's kind of how things
have been playing out for me.
Well, for me,
it's more like "cry now,
"cry later."
Wanna hear a joke?
Uh, I don't know. Is it funny?
Not really.
Great. Go for it.
What kind of tea
is hard to drink?
I don't know.
Reali-ty.
Yeah. Wow. Well, that's...
- (CHUCKLES)
- That's something.
I'll keep working on it.
Hey, time
for your group session.
Here he comes,
like fucking clockwork.
What's your name?
I'm Eric.
Shelly.
I'll see you around, Shelly.
(PLATE CLATTERS)
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
THERAPIST: If you were
forced to be silent,
step into the circle.
If you were made
to feel that anything wrong
is your fault,
step into the circle.
If you were abandoned,
neglected, manipulated
by those who were
meant to protect you,
step into the circle.
If you are ready to look forward
to the good things
that life will bring you,
step into the circle.
We're pleased you found her.
We're so fond of you
and your daughter.
You all right?
Oh, hey. Yeah.
Fuck, they really
trashed the place, huh?
Um... Yeah.
Is this me?
(CHUCKLES)
All right.
These songs or poems?
I wouldn't call them either.
It's just shit that I write.
(ERIC SIGHS NERVOUSLY)
You write beautifully.
Some of this would be great
set to music.
Do you play music?
Used to.
Well, maybe we could, um...
I don't know, maybe, um...
Maybe we could
play together sometime.
Maybe.
See how we get along.
What are you doing in here?
I don't know.
I guess everything
just finally caught up with me.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
MAN: (ON PA)
Patient 005, Shelly,
please be advised
you have a visitor.
No one knows I'm here.
Hey. I'll go have a look, okay?
I mean, it just looks
like fucking lawyers to me.
Come on, take a look.
SHELLY: (WHISPERS)
What the fuck?
- (BREATH TREMBLING)
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Who are they?
- They can't find me here.
If they find me here,
I'm fucked.
Her room is right this way.
- I've got to get out of here.
- Yeah, yeah.
- They can't find me here.
- Um...
- Fuck!
- Come with me.
Could you give me a location
update on Patient 005?
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Okay, here it is. You see
those windows up there?
- Yeah.
- They'll take you out to the yard.
- Okay.
- Wait, wait, wait.
You gotta get the tag off.
(TAG BEEPS)
Can you pick up their signal?
WOMAN: (ON RADIO)
They're in the laundry room.
(SHELLY GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
What're you doing?
Fuck this place.
I'm rehabilitated.
(TAG BEEPS)
(DISORDER BY JOY DIVISION
PLAYING)
♪ I've been waiting for a guide
♪ To come
and take me by the hand
♪ Could these sensations
make me feel
♪ The pleasures
of a normal man?
♪ Lose sensations,
spare the insults
♪ Leave them for another day
♪ I've got the spirit
Lose the feeling
♪ Take the shock away ♪
Think we fucking did it.
(CHUCKLES)
(ERIC WHOOPING)
ERIC: Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, slow, slow down.
- Stop.
- (SONG FADES OUT)
Who were those people?
A former life.
Right.
Got one of those.
I bet you do.
(MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
(ELEVATOR DOOR CLOSES)
Jesus, this is crazy.
It's my friend's place.
He lives in Antigua.
Lets me crash here sometimes.
So, um...
What now?
You know,
you don't have to stay.
Maybe it's safer if you don't.
I want to stay.
Okay. Well, then,
we'll hide out here for a while.
And then what?
We'll hide somewhere else.
Just figure it out.
Good plan.
It is a good plan.
You stink, dude.
- I'm sorry.
- (CHUCKLES)
Do you mind if I use the shower?
Not yet.
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
(ERIC MOANS)
(LAUGHING)
Pretty good.
What's the first thing
you liked about me
when you saw me?
What's, um...
(BOTH LAUGHING)
There's like an aura about you.
It feels powerful.
What's the first thing
you liked about me?
I thought that you were
quite brilliantly broken.
You are.
(SHELLY CHUCKLES)
What's the, um...
What's the worst thing
you've ever done?
I once escaped rehab with
a complete fucking degenerate.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Probably the best thing
I've ever done.
SHELLY: Mm.
Wait, I just
remembered something.
(CUPBOARD SCRAPES)
(SHELLY CHUCKLES)
You have a secret stash here?
All right.
Hello.
Aha.
- Those are the ones?
- Mm-hmm.
Lamb of God.
- (CORK POPS)
- (SHELLY YELPS, LAUGHS)
(FALL BY THE BUG
FT. INGA COPELAND PLAYING)
Stop looking at me
or I'll poke your eye out.
- Poke out my eye?
- Mm-hmm. You don't need that.
You've got me now.
♪ The rise and fall
♪ Of your God
- (SHELLY SCREAMS)
- ♪ Will tell me the story
- ♪ I've been missing
- (BOTH LAUGHING)
♪ Let the game begin
♪ Let us lose or win
♪ Let's rise
♪ The rise and fall
♪ Of your God
♪ Will tell me the story
of your city
♪ The rise and fall ♪
(SONG FADES)
How many people have you loved?
Like seriously, seriously loved?
ERIC: Mm.
Me neither.
Promise me something.
What?
If I'm ever hard to love,
try to love me harder.
(MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
(ERIC GRUNTS)
(MUSIC TURNING OMINOUS)
(SIREN BLARING)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(KEYPAD CLACKING)
(LINE RINGING)
Marion.
You have a problem.
(CHOPIN'S PRELUDE NO.15
PLAYING ON PIANO)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Call for you, Mr. Roeg.
MR. ROEG: Yes?
They found Zadie's body.
And here I thought
there was nothing left to find.
It's a setback, but we're close
on one of the others.
If this video gets out,
you know what they'll do to me.
I find this tiresome, Marion.
This running around.
I can feel you sweating
through the phone.
This ends here.
(CONTINUES PLAYING PIANO)
(MUSIC ENDS)
(THIN FLESH BY TRAITRS PLAYING)
MAN 1: You're infatuated.
You're obsessed, bro.
- SHELLY: Hi.
- Hi.
What are you reading?
Rimbaud.
Shall I read you some?
- Yeah.
(CHUCKLES)
(THIN FLESH BY TRAITRS
CONTINUES PLAYING)
MAN 2: Hell yeah!
(SONG GETS MUFFLED)
(SERENE MUSIC PLAYING)
I don't want it to end.
Doesn't have to.
We could be living like this
all the fucking time.
- (TRAINS RUMBLING)
- (BELL CLANGING)
(TRAIN HORN BLARES)
(MELLOW PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
SHELLY:
♪ Take me down to the
♪ The sun's out there shining
♪ But my head's in my hands
♪ I'm a sucker for hiding
♪ A pretty sucker I... ♪
Why'd you stop?
That was beautiful.
SHELLY: Mm...
Why don't you play?
No. We both know
you're better at this than me.
SHELLY: No. No, no, no.
Please, please.
ERIC: Yes. Go on.
- (SHELLY WHIMPERS)
- (ERIC CHUCKLES)
(PLAYING MELLOW TUNE)
(JARRING, OVERLAPPING SOUNDS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(DEMONIC WHISPERING)
(SHELLY GASPS)
I can't do this right now.
Okay.
You all right? What's going on?
Could we just go out for a bit?
I haven't played piano
for a while.
I loved playing.
It was my whole life.
But my mom took it
and twisted it all,
pushed me
into performing at places
I was too young to be at.
Didn't want to play
for any of them.
I saw things.
I shouldn't have seen any of it.
I hurt people.
(SOFTLY) And I just...
I know.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
What did you do?
I can't tell you.
If you knew, you'd leave me.
And if you left me, I'd die.
If I left you,
I'd already be dead.
I just want to start over.
Well, why don't we?
Where would we go?
Fuckin' anywhere.
Anywhere is better
than this fucking place.
Anywhere?
ERIC: Anywhere.
SHELLY: So you're saying
if I jumped,
you'd jump with me.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
Of course I would.
Do you think angsty teens
would build
little shrines for us?
Yeah. They'd be lining up
to leave cigarettes and whiskey.
No.
No?
Lilies.
A sea of white lilies.
All right. Lilies, it is.
(UP-TEMPO ELECTRONIC DANCE
MUSIC PLAYING)
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SHELLY LAUGHING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES INSIDE)
ERIC: I told you, bro.
I fucking love this guy!
SHELLY: I'm gonna go
and get some water.
I can get it for you.
No, no. You stay there.
Sure.
SHELLY: Can I get
some water, please?
Shelly! Shelly!
- Dom... What the fuck?
- Just listen to me.
Just listen to me. Just listen.
Zadie's dead.
They're gonna
come for us, Shelly.
You need to leave town now.
SHELLY: What do you mean?
DOM: Shelly, you gotta
listen to me. It's true.
SHELLY: No, no, no.
I'm not leaving without Eric.
DOM: No.
Shelly, just listen to me.
Are you hearing what I'm saying?
Zadie's fucking dead!
- Come on, we've gotta leave.
- What's going on?
- We've gotta leave, Eric.
- Who the fuck was that?
SHELLY: I'll tell you
everything.
Let's just get back
to your place.
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(ELEVATOR WHIRRING)
(RUSTLING SOFTLY)
(SHELLY YELLS)
- Shelly?
- (SHELLY YELLS)
- Shelly!
- (MUFFLED GROANING)
Get off her! Get off her!
No, don't do this.
No, please don't do this.
Get off of her!
Please don't do this.
(YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
(ERIC AND SHELLY GROANING)
(GASPING)
(WHEEZING)
(GASPING LABORIOUSLY)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(WHEEZING LABORIOUSLY)
(BREATHING STOPS)
(SMOOCHES)
(MUFFLED WHEEZING)
(CONTINUES WHEEZING)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPING)
(COUGHING)
(PANTING)
What the fuck!
Shelly?
(DOG WHINING SOFTLY)
(DOG BARKING)
Hey.
Hey!
(ERIC GROANS)
Hey?
(CROWS CAWING)
(ECHOING) Hey!
Where am I?
What is this place?
You'd think they'd come up
with something better,
wouldn't you?
But you know,
they don't expect us to linger.
How long we stay here
is entirely up to you.
(CROWS CAWING)
(ECHOING WHISPER) ...we stay
here is entirely up to you.
(MUTED WHISPERING)
What the fuck
is happening to me?
People once believed
when someone dies,
a crow carries their soul
to the land of the dead.
But sometimes,
something so bad happens
that a terrible sadness
is carried with it...
and the soul cannot rest.
(CAWING)
What are you talking about?
The crow will guide you
to put the wrong things right.
What do you mean?
Oh, fuck this. This isn't real.
(LAUGHS)
You stay the fuck away from me.
There's nothing there but here.
ERIC: This is all
just a fucking nightmare.
This is just
a fucking nightmare.
- (GASPS)
- Then go wake up.
ERIC: The sadness is killing...
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
Shelly?
(GROANS)
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHIRRING)
My turn.
Come on, Shelly.
You don't respect my art.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(DOOR OPENS)
MAN: I'm here.
What am I looking for exactly?
MARION: Her cell phone.
MAN: All right.
MARION: We looked,
but we were interrupted.
MAN: What's on it?
MARION: You don't need to know.
Just find it.
MAN: All right. All right.
You can come out, boy.
ERIC: Who are you?
I'm a cop.
Here.
Come on.
ERIC: Okay.
COP: It's okay.
- Drop that. Drop that.
- Yeah.
(KNIFE CLATTERS)
Listen, I think I'm going crazy.
I don't know what's real
or not anymore.
I just think
something really bad
has happened with my girlfriend.
(GRUNTS)
Fuck.
(GROANS)
What the fuck?
Oh, fuck.
(GRUNTS)
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(ERIC GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH STRAINING)
(ERIC YELLS)
(ERIC GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
(ERIC GRUNTS)
(INTENSE MUSIC FADES)
(STRAINED GRUNT)
(COP GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(GROANING)
Oh, no.
(SQUELCHING)
Ah, what the fuck!
What the fuck!
- (SQUELCHES)
- (SCREAMING)
- (DOOR CLANGS)
- (THUNDER RUMBLES)
MYSTERIOUS MAN: (ECHOING) The crow will guide you
to put the wrong things right.
- ...wrong things right.
- (CROW CAWING)
The crow will guide you
to put the wrong things right.
People once believed...
People once believed
when someone dies,
a crow carries their soul
to the land of the dead.
But sometimes,
something so bad happens
that a terrible sadness
is carried with it.
And the soul cannot rest.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
...will guide you.
And the soul cannot rest.
Shelly?
Shelly, baby.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's okay.
It's okay. Don't...
Look, come down from there.
It's okay. No, no, no, no, no!
No!
(GASPS)
(CROWS CAWING)
She's dead, isn't she?
We're both dead.
I'm afraid so.
(SNIFFLES)
What are you?
Some kind of angel?
(LAUGHS)
Do I look like an angel?
ERIC: I don't understand.
Why am I here and she isn't?
You're not gonna
like the answer.
Just tell me.
She's on her way down.
To a place far worse than this.
You said I could make
the wrong things right.
What does that mean?
The one who killed you is not supposed
to be in your world.
They made a deal with the devil
to gain eternal life
by sending the innocent to hell.
That's not balance.
Kill them.
Kill them all.
And you get your lives back.
You're saying
I can get her back?
Yeah.
Kill the ones who killed you,
and you will get her back.
(CAWING)
When I was up there,
I got shot.
And it taught you something,
didn't it?
What I, um... I can heal?
I can't die?
Your body? No.
Feel pain? Yes.
If your love remains pure,
you cannot die.
How am I supposed to trust you?
Do you have another choice?
Are you ready?
Holy shit.
Eric, what the fuck?
Where have you been?
Everyone thought you was dead.
Everyone was right.
Very funny. Just come inside.
I need your help, man.
What do you need?
I need a gun.
A gun.
Eric, what...
What are you gonna do with a...
You know what, it's not my...
You're going to need these.
- (BELL TOLLING)
- (CROW CAWING)
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
I'm a friend of your daughter's.
We need to talk.
Who was after her?
Why did you
come for her that day?
I saw you there
with the people who killed her.
What are you talking about?
It was an overdose.
How would you know?
Because I was there.
You don't understand
who you're dealing with.
I loved her.
I need to know
who these people are
because I'm going to kill them.
Every single one of them.
And I'm gonna bring her back.
She's not coming back.
My baby's gone.
She's gone.
And she's not coming back.
(CRYING)
Please leave me.
Just stop.
(CONTINUES CRYING) She's gone.
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING)
(EXHALES)
(SNIFFING)
(SCRAPING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC BUILDING)
(M.E. BY GARY NUMAN PLAYING)
♪ And m.e. I eat dust
♪ We're all so run down
♪ I'd call it my death
♪ But I'll only fade away
♪ And I hate to fade alone
♪ Now there's only m.e.
I fucking killed you.
Yeah. You did.
Don't move.
♪ We were so wrong
♪ Now it's over
♪ But there's no one
left to see
Turn it off.
♪ And there's no one... ♪
(MUSIC STOPS)
I want names
of all the people
that you work for.
Don't!
(SIZZLING)
- (EARS RINGING)
- (MUFFLED) Fuck!
(TINNITUS BUZZING)
(GROANING)
(RINGING FADES)
(PHONE DINGING)
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
Get down!
- Drive!
- (TIRES SCREECHING)
- (WHIMPERING)
- (GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(CAR HORN BLARES)
- (GASPING)
- (GROANS)
Get in the back!
(YELPS)
(HORN HONKING)
(GRUNTS)
- (ERIC GRUNTS)
- (TRUCK HORN HONKING)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTING WEAKLY)
(GROANS)
(BONES CRUNCHING)
(ERIC GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (BONES CRACK)
- (SCREAMS)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hello, Sophia.
I'm sorry it's been so long.
Truly.
My condolences.
Shelly was such a special girl.
I heard you had a visitor.
(ANGRILY) What did he want?
He wants to kill you.
Oh. Anger.
First impulse. (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
It's not anger.
What is it, then?
Love.
Loved her so much.
He told me he was going
to bring her back.
What was that?
He thinks if he kills you,
he'll be able to bring
her back from the dead.
(UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, Shelly.
So many times you needed me,
and I was never there.
Stop it.
She's gone.
You traded her
for a better life.
That took a lot of courage.
What you gave me was not a gift,
it was a curse.
I would rather have died.
Well, then you should
go and be with her.
(DEMONIC WHISPERING)
(BODY THUDS)
(PASSERBY SCREAMING)
PASSERBY: No!
(PASSERSBY CLAMORING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(KEYPAD BEEPING)
(LINE RINGING)
- Marion.
- Yes?
He has been sent back.
The power to escape death
exists within him.
Bring him to me.
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
- (TRAIN RUMBLING)
- (TRAIN HORN HONKS)
Fuck.
I'm just... Don't hurt me, man.
- Please.
- Why the fuck not?
- I didn't do anything, man.
- I saw you.
- What?
- In the club.
You brought them to us.
No, no. I was just
trying to get her out.
I was just trying
to help her get away, man.
Get away from what? Huh?
That woman who was after her,
who is she?
Who, Marion?
No. No. She's just part of it.
She just works for him.
Who are you talking about? Who?
His name is Vincent Roeg, man.
He used to have us
over to party.
I thought it was just
an easy place to score.
That shit got so dark.
He made it so dark.
He's got this voice, man.
Voice.
He... burrows inside you.
Finds the darkest parts
of your soul
and gives them a voice.
And it just gets
louder and louder
until you do something evil.
I still hear it.
I never would have
made that fucking video
if I'd known
what would have happened, man.
What video?
Where is it?
Shelly had it on her phone.
Said she had it hidden.
She didn't want
anyone to see it.
I tried to warn her,
but she wouldn't leave without you.
I knew Shelly a long time.
When I saw the way
she looked at you,
something was different.
I tried to do
something right, man.
I just fucked it up.
I'm sorry.
They won't be far behind me.
You do what we couldn't do.
Get the fuck out.
Thanks, man.
(TRAIN APPROACHING)
- (THUNDER RUMBLES)
- (CAWS)
(ELEVATOR DOOR CLOSES)
(WISTFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
SHELLY: How many people
have you loved?
Like seriously,
seriously loved?
(SHELLY LAUGHING)
(LAUGHTER ON VIDEO)
WOMAN: Oh, stop!
- I will come back.
- (BOTH LAUGHING)
(UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
WOMAN 2: What the fuck!
ZADIE: What did you do to her?
Oh, my God,
there's blood everywhere.
What the fuck, Shelly? Help me!
She's dying.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- (PHONE CLATTERS)
- Oh... (WINCES)
Oh...
Oh... (BREATHING HEAVILY)
(TOTAL DEPRAVITY
BY THE VEILS PLAYING)
(CROW CAWS)
(CROW CAWING)
♪ I asked our father
and he said
♪ It don't get no easier
once you're dead
♪ This whole universe
is just mud and bone
♪ And you carry
what you can alone
♪ There's total depravity
♪ Staring back at me ♪
(CAWS)
(MUSIC STOPS)
ERIC: I found
what they killed her for.
Shelly, she did something
really bad.
And now I can't get it
out of my head.
I don't think I can do this.
I don't think
I can do this, man.
Eric, you just need
to sit down, bro.
- Fuck.
- Eric, sit down, please.
Please. Eric, come on.
Come on. Just sit down.
What's going on?
Holy shit.
Why didn't she just
fucking tell me?
She should have
just fucking told me.
Okay, but, if she did tell you,
could you still love her?
(DISTANT THUD)
Eric?
What the fuck?
You need to come with us.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(ERIC GROANING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
- (ERIC YELLS)
- (GRUNTS)
Fuck.
(GASPS)
- (KNIFE STABBING)
- (WOMAN SCREAMING)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
What the fuck have you done?
(SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES)
(GASPING)
(CROW CAWING)
(PANTING)
Why am I back here?
MYSTERIOUS MAN:
You couldn't see it through.
Hey. Why...
Why did I stop healing?
I said your love
needed to remain pure.
The enemy of love is not hate.
It's doubt.
I never doubted her.
Didn't you?
You had a chance
and you wasted it.
You were given
the power of a god.
In the end, you were just a boy.
At least your soul can move on.
Her soul is gone forever
into the darkness.
For you, eternity is easy.
You just have to breathe.
And let her go.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Mine for hers.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
My soul for hers.
Her soul is damned.
The place she's going,
you can't imagine it.
It's not about me.
Even if you save her,
you will never
be with her again.
I know.
Now let me do this.
(CROWS CAWING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
It's not up to me.
- (THUD)
- (GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
There is no going back
from this.
(GROANS)
(CHANTING INDISTINCTLY)
(ERIC GROANS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS LOUDLY)
With this black blood,
you will move between worlds,
just like them.
Go put the wrong things right.
(ROGUISH ELECTRONIC
MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
- (GUN CLATTERS)
- (MUSIC STOPS)
Hold this.
Hmm.
(BOADICEA BY ENYA PLAYING)
(WHIRRING)
(SWORD CLINKS)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
Marion.
Vincent.
VINCENT: Is it true?
MARION: I'm afraid so.
He was killed.
Are you sure?
I'm sorry.
Damn.
(CAWING)
(SONG FADES)
USHER: Please can we ask you
to make your way
to your seats. Thank you.
Stefan?
Front entrance secure.
(AUDIENCE CLAPPING)
(ORCHESTRA PLAYING
ROBERT LE DIABLE OPERA)
(TENOR SINGING)
(GRUNTING)
(SOPRANO SINGING)
(SINGING CONTINUES)
(GUN SAFETY CLICKS)
(SINGING TURNS DRAMATIC)
(YELLS)
(SINGING STOPS)
(DULCET MUSIC PLAYING)
(SWORD CLINKS)
- ERIC: Hey!
- (MUSIC TURNS DRAMATIC)
- (ERIC GRUNTS)
- (GROANING)
(MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
(STRAINING)
HENCHMAN: We have a situation.
(OPERATIC SINGING RESUMES)
MAN: He's here.
(OPERATIC MUSIC SOARS)
(HISSING)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(GUNSHOTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (ERIC GRUNTS)
- (BONES CRACK)
(GUNSHOTS)
(OPERATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
(MUSIC PAUSES)
- (MUSIC RESUMES)
- (YELLING)
(SCREAMS)
(SWORD CLATTERS)
(GRUNTING)
- (YELLS)
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (SCREAMS)
- (FLESH SQUELCHING)
(EXHALES)
(YELLS)
(OPERATIC MUSIC ENDS)
(AUDIENCE CLAPPING)
(TENOR SINGING ARIA)
(SIGHING)
(SOFTLY) He's here.
He's killing all of our people.
I'm so grateful to you, Marion.
For what? Wh...
VINCENT:
For getting us this far.
That's all you're going to say?
We're on this ride
together, Marion.
You just happen
to be in the front.
(DRAMATIC OPERATIC
MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCREAMING)
(YELLS)
(EXHALES)
(MARION GASPING)
Where is he?
He's not in here.
(GASPING) He's...
(WHIMPERING)
His country estate.
Hillhurst Manor.
You fucking killed us.
For what?
Was it worth it?
It starts off so small.
It's all kept from you.
You know what's being done,
but you're not part of it.
And then, just like that,
you are.
You're swallowed up.
And the only direction
you can go is down.
You have the same look as him.
What look is that?
The look of someone who hates
everything inside of him.
He just hides it
better than you.
(DRAMATIC OPERATIC
MUSIC CONTINUES)
- (SWORD SLASHES)
- (OPERA ENDS)
(AUDIENCE SCREAMING)
(HEADS THUD)
(MEANING (CHORAL VERSION)
(BY CASCADEUR PLAYING)
♪ I'm a strange man
♪ Like your angel
♪ I'm invisible
♪ Like a monster
♪ But someday you'll understand
SHELLY: Lilies.
A sea of white lilies.
♪ The meaning of my life
♪ But someday you'll understand
♪ The meaning of these words
(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
♪ I'm the speaker
♪ Of your silence
(ENGINE REVVING)
♪ I'm the question now
♪ Of your silence
♪ To your answer
♪ But someday you'll understand
♪ The meaning of my life
♪ The meaning of these words
♪ But someday you'll understand
(CAWING)
♪ The meaning of my life
♪ But someday you'll understand
♪ The meaning of these words
♪ Oh
♪ The meaning of your life ♪
(SONG ENDS)
(CAWING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Face me.
Who are you?
Just an old man...
but I'm real.
(SLASHES)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
See?
I'm flesh and blood.
Not like you.
I heard you think
you can bring her back.
You can't.
Where she is,
you don't come back from that.
That video, did you see it?
I know, I'm sorry.
She's not what
you thought she was.
No, it wasn't her.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
It was you.
You corrupt people.
You can't corrupt
what's not already there.
A pearl. It's a seed.
ERIC: Hmm.
Look at yourself.
Look at what you've become.
Those eyes.
That face.
Why would she want
to be with you?
You have no love left.
Only hate.
You fool.
- (SQUELCHES)
- (GRUNTS SOFTLY)
You don't feel anything.
Do you?
You don't feel any of it.
I feel it all.
(ERIC GRUNTS)
(DEMONIC WHISPERING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GASPS)
INMATE: Say something!
- Wake the fuck up.
- Say something, man!
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
VINCENT: You have no love left.
Only hate.
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING)
She's not what
you thought she was.
(CAWING)
- (SHRIEKS)
- (SCREAMS)
(EXHALES)
(GROANS)
(GROWLS)
SHELLY: When I'm hard to love,
love me harder.
Love me harder.
How many people have you loved?
Like seriously,
seriously loved?
Don't leave me.
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
I don't want it to end.
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROWLS)
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(YELLING)
(CROWS CAWING)
What is this place?
ERIC: This is the place
where it all ends.
Where you pay
for what you did to her...
to all of them.
(GRUNTS)
Are you scared?
You should be.
(CAWS)
Oh, you stupid boy.
Is this what you want?
You think she's worth it?
All this?
Eternal hell?
For what?
For some fucking whore?
(GRUNTING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(YELLS)
You have no idea
what hell awaits you.
Yeah, I do.
(ERIC YELLS)
(DARK MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(CROWS CAWING)
(EXHALES)
(FAINT ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPS)
(SHELLY GRUNTS)
SHELLY: Eric.
I had this terrible dream.
I was falling.
I thought I'd lost you.
ERIC: It's okay, baby.
It's over.
It's all over.
You get to go back.
Eric...
what have you done?
I can't come with you.
What?
This was the only way.
- (FAINT THUD)
- (SHELLY GASPS)
No.
I'm going with you.
This isn't the way
it was supposed to end.
I would do it again.
All of it.
Every moment.
- (FAINT THUD)
- (SHELLY GASPS)
I love you.
Forever.
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
Do you hear me?
Yes.
It's okay.
He fought hard for you.
(WHIMPERS)
(MOURNFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(CRYING)
(CROWS CAWING)
(PANTING)
ERIC: Our love
will live on
in everything she does.
(CHUCKLES)
(BOTH LAUGH)
Someday, I know...
our souls
will find each other again.
(ROUSING MUSIC PLAYING)
Till then,
I will have just the memory.
That perfect sensation
of loving her.
And that's enough.
Almost enough.
(CROW CAWING)
(WHAT WENT DOWN
BY FOALS PLAYING)
♪ I buried my heart
in a hole in the ground
♪ They tried to call my girl
♪ But she could not be found
♪ I buried my guilt
in a pit in the sound
♪ With the rust
and the vultures
♪ And the trash downtown
♪ So don't step to me, kid
♪ You'll never be found
♪ 'Cause while
you were sleeping
♪ I took over your town
♪ When I see a man,
I see a lion
♪ You're the apple of my eye
♪ Of my eye, of my eye
♪ Of my eye, I want ya
♪ I fell for a girl
with a port-wine stain
♪ I knew her initials
♪ But never her name
♪ I tried and I tried
♪ And I was never the same
♪ So no longer felt love
♪ And I'm forever changed
♪ When I see a man,
I see a lion
♪ You're the apple of my eye
♪ Of my eye, of my eye
♪ Of my eye, I want ya ♪
(SONG ENDS)
(INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)